<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.pdfzero.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.pdfzero.com/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-08-18T21:58:13-05:00</updated><id>https://www.pdfzero.com/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">PDFZero</title><author><name>PDFZero</name></author><entry><title type="html">Why did you change</title><link href="https://www.pdfzero.com/blog/why-did-you-change.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why did you change" /><published>0001-01-01T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>0001-01-01T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://www.pdfzero.com/blog/why-did-you-change</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.pdfzero.com/blog/why-did-you-change.html">&lt;p&gt;
  The original version of PDFZero was cloud-based, meaning that your files needed to be sent to our servers for processing before you could download the edited files. We always believed that a privacy-first approach (i.e. never having your files leave your computer) was preferred. However, we didn't know how to make that happen at the time. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Eventually, we discovered some new open-source software that made our preferred privacy-first approach possible. Using these tools, we build the new version of PDFZero. Now, your files never leave your computer. When you download a tool webpage, you download the tool &lt;em&gt;itself&lt;/em&gt;. All PDF processing happens on your computer, so your documents don't need to be sent off to the cloud. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  A lot of development time went into building the PDF libraries we used before, and replicating that in the browser is both hard and time consuming. For more complicated PDFs, that may mean that these tools are not as robust. However, we are dedicated to imporoving the tools and fixing bugs as quickly as we can. If our tools do not work on your PDFs, let us know! 
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>PDFZero</name></author><summary type="html">The original version of PDFZero was cloud-based, meaning that your files needed to be sent to our servers for processing before you could download the edited files. We always believed that a privacy-first approach (i.e. never having your files leave your computer) was preferred. However, we didn't know how to make that happen at the time.</summary></entry></feed>